One Winter Weekend is a romance, tv movie film directed by Gary Yates.
Cara, a women’s magazine writer, who gets burned by her boyfriend
on New Years’ Eve, decides to go on a dating detox.
Challenged by her employer to write about it, she hopes a spontaneous
ski getaway with her best friend will spark inspiration.
Complicating matters, they discover they’ve double booked their chalet
with two eligible men, including Ben, an entrepreneur.
When the share-mates get snowed in, Cara and Ben are thrown together.
Cara, played by Taylor Cole.
Ben, played by Jack Turner.
Jennifer, played by Bea Santos.
Megan, played by Rukiya Bernard.
Shawn, played by Dewshane Williams.
Diane, played by Kristen Harris.
This is a list of films which placed number one at the
weekend box office for the year 2018.
The film explores themes of winter, chalet, ski resort, ski, christmas.
The tone is emotional.